https://www.eyesave.com/privacy/

Brands
Gabriel + SimoneFendi Optical FramesPrada Optical FramesPersolTom Ford OpticalGucci Optical FramesKate Spade Optical FramesChristian DiorAble VisionTom Ford
View all brands
Additional Information
Additional Information
Home
Contact
FAQ
Guarantee
Privacy
Change Currency
Loading... Please wait...
Call us on
My Account
Sign in or Create an account
Search
Contact
FAQ
Guarantee
Privacy
Brands
Gabriel + SimoneFendi Optical FramesPrada Optical FramesPersolTom Ford OpticalGucci Optical FramesKate Spade Optical FramesChristian DiorAble VisionTom Ford
View all brands
HomePrivacy
Privacy
PRIVACY STATEMENT FOR EYESAVE.COM
At EyeSave.com we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you as set forth in the policy below, to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
How does EyeSave.com protect customer information? When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
Will EyeSave.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties? What about "cookies"? "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. We may use technologies such as our own cookies to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests.  To opt out of this advertising, click here. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use all of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them.
EyeSave.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others without your prior consent. Occasionally we may send you an email regarding a special promotion that we are running, but you can tell us not to by sending a e-mail message stating for us to remove you from our e-mail list to info@eyesave.com. (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use). Also, EyeSave.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. EyeSave.com may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of EyeSave.com, our users, or others.
What personal information is collected? Your email, phone number, address...etc. are collected on EyeSave.com in order to process your order and ship it correctly. We also use this information to contact you if there is a problem.
What navigational information is collected and how is it used? EyeSave.com collects the user's Internet Protocol Address (IP) which is a number that is automatically assigned to your PC everytime you browse the Internet. This information is only used in the aggregate form and IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information. Additionally, we use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider please click here.
How do users modify their personal information? Users can log into YOUR ACCOUNT on our website or they can email info@eyesave.com with any changes to their personal information and or order.
In summary We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at EyeSave.com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others without your prior consent.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact info@eyesave.com.
Thank You
Further info
Contact
FAQ
Guarantee
Privacy
Shipping
Returns
Brands
Gabriel + SimoneFendi Optical FramesPrada Optical FramesPersolTom Ford OpticalGucci Optical FramesKate Spade Optical FramesChristian DiorAble VisionTom Ford
View all brands
Connect with us
Pinterest
Instagram
Twitter
Facebook
All prices are in USD. © 2020 EyeSave | Sitemap
|
